

Mohith Kumar S S

+91 7349577840 ssmohithkumar@gmail.com. 04 - 10 - 2002



Profile

I am an entry-level Software Engineer and Programmer, currently pursuing Bachelor's at APS college of Engineering, Bengaluru, Karnataka with a major in Computer Science Engineering. An all-time tech Enthusiast who loves to create new things to solve real-world problems which can create impact on the society. My major interest is in Front-end development, UI/UX designing, Web development, Artificial Intelligence, DBMS, Cyber Security, Networking.

A beginner coder in Python, Javascript, React Native. Expert in HTML, CSS, C, C++, Java. An avid Influencer and fluent in English, Hindi and Kannada.

Project Experience

INSTRUMENTAL DATABASE - 2022

Designed a DataBase which can maintain the data and other information fead to it with the help of MySql, HTML5, CSS and JavaScript. For Back-end, have used MySql and for front-end have used HTML5, CSS and JavaScript.

APSCE - DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM - 2022 - 23

Designed a DataBase in which we can manage the students data with the help of teacher's interface. Provided an interface for student by which they can easily see their stats. Attendance and monitoring made easy.

DRONE - COLLISION AVOIDANCE - 2022 - 23

Designing a Drone which can fly autonomously after setting the destination, on the path towards destination, if the Drone detects the obstacle, by using the algorithm and the sensors it can avoid the collusion.

NWRTC - VEHICLE TRACKER - 2022

Designed an App using Flutter which can track the location of the vehicle and maintain a schedule of the vehicle.

APSCE - WEBSITE - 2021 - 22

Designed and Developed a Professional website for my institution APSCE, which is currently in use. Used HTML5, CSS and JavaScript to increase user experience.

MINI BOT - 2019 - 2020 (PRE - UNIVERSITY)

Created a Project call Mini Bot which can move from one place to another with the help of a controller and a Network. Used AI to communicate and talk with users just like Google Assistant.

ALGORITHM DESIGN - 2018 (PRE - UNIVERSITY)

Developed an algorithm which can compute the complexity of a program execution.



Education

APS College Of Engineering - BE in Computer Science and Engineering (2020 - 24)

PES University - Pre - University (2018 - 20)

APS High School - Schooling (2015 - 18)



Skills

Teaching, Leadership, Influencer, Counselor, Team Building, Marketing, Graphic Designer, Photographer, Vector Arts Creator, Arts Creator, Counselor, CouVideo Creator, Editor, Singer, Web Designer, Front End Developer, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Content creator, Quick learner.